Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Asa and Yuno have both beaten the odds and passed the Magic Knight's entrance exam.
Wind magic. Towering tornado!
Number 164!
Wait! All of them? Impossible!
It would be an honor to join the Golden Dawn.
Number 165! No hands.
There's no real surprise, is it?
What would anyone ever want with you? A kid with zero magic.
I won't give up! No! I will become the Wizard King!
You know, kid, I like you. Come join our crew.
With their acceptance into Magic Knight's squads, the two young men have taken the first step toward becoming the Wizard King.
I'm the newest member of this squad! Fresh from Hajj Village!
Austin!
Aw, whoops.
This is us. The worst of the worst Magic Knight squads. Welcome to the Black Bulls.
The Black Bulls.
Iskara Cunnitous Continue to see you again?
It's your ownHH.
The Hispanic whiskeyiest Package stream.
for hell to get them
they'll stop
I'm this one
a little wymone
theetter
them
or
I
I'll continue to create you
I'll tell you, I'll tell you, and I'll tell you
It's like one page like you and me
I've met you and I
I'll tell you this is a miracle
What's your name?
You know
Well, my name is Klaus Lunetz
A commoner from a tiny village
Somebody who is of neither royal nor noble birth
What was Captain Vontian's thinking letting you in?
Don't get cocky just because all of the captains raised their hands for you
It means nothing
You'll need more than that to be accepted as a true knight of the Golden Dawn
I'm certain I'll prove myself soon enough
Watch that smart mouth
No! I'm not done!
Okay, now I'm real mad
You ready to take me on?
Nope, not really
But let's go!
Why is it so loud in here?
I should have skipped those extra drinks
My head is killing me
Oh precious, perfect little Marie
My dear sister.
My love.
Enough! Shut up, damn you!
Jeez, make it stop.
My poor head.
Looks like they're at it again.
Man, these guys are scary.
Still, I'm one of them now.
I'd better act like it.
I'm Asta from Haas Village!
I'm a black bull now, too!
Someday!
I'm gonna become the Wizard King!
That brand you were serving is super tasty!
Good, because that's the last thing you'll ever eat!
Come on, give it a rest, you idiots!
You're going to wake up my sister with all the noise you're making!
Damn it!
Oh, get over it, you freaky sister lover!
Let's see.
I remember getting into a drinking contest with some guy,
but after that...
Perfect, thank you!
I'm totally not listening.
Oh!
You stole from me!
My fault!
Mine!
Argh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Ugh!
Will you please shut up?
I've got the mother of all headaches!
That's your own fault, you drunk!
What did you say?
Oh, you heard me!
At least I'm not a virgin street punk!
Virgin street punk?
Where do you get off calling me that?
You better be careful!
Get distracted and I'll get you!
Oh, yeah?
Then come back here and give it your best shot!
Come on!
I told you to shut up!
In the name of my angelic sister Marie, I will destroy you both!
No, no!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
All right.
I've had enough.
Quit breaking stuff already!
Oh, man!
Now it's way broken!
Huh?
Captain!
What is that?
How was it?
Did you find us an arrogant newbie?
I can take him down a notch or two.
Ow!
Please, sir!
Can I go up against you today?
Come on!
Don't hold back!
Now, now.
Forget all about these little brats.
Wouldn't you rather come out for a drink with me?
Hey, hey!
Try this!
It's really good!
Take a big bite!
Go on!
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
May I please go see my sister?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Yeah, yeah.
Glad to know how much you missed me.
Now shut up, will ya?
Sorry, sir.
I'd like you all to meet our new, uh...
Where'd he go?
Over there.
Help me!
I can't breathe!
Quit messing around.
I'll just pass out now.
Now, like I was saying, this shrimp here is our other new member.
What do you mean, other?
Go on, tell him your name or something.
Yes, sir!
My name's Asta from Hajj Village!
It's really nice to meet everyone!
You're from Hajj?
That's out in the middle of nowhere.
Finral, introduce everyone, will ya?
Sure thing, sir.
Let's see, where to start?
You know Gordon Agrippa?
I see.
Not always the easiest guy to talk to, but he's good people.
Next we have...
Vanessa Enoteca.
Tends to pick fights when she's drunk, but she's good people.
Picking fights, I don't know what you're talking about.
Hajj Village.
Way off on the outskirts of the kingdom?
Yeah!
Hmm...
To make your way from a tiny little backwater village to a magic night squad?
You must've worked so hard.
Nice kiddo.
What do you say I give you something as a reward, huh?
Man, that's hard to turn down!
But my heart is set on Sister Lily and I will stay true to her no matter what!
Alright, let's continue, shall we?
Hey, do me next!
Luck Voltia, a battle freak who's addicted to fighting.
But he's good people.
Nice meeting you!
So hey, do you like to fight?
Uh, sure.
Yeah, that's cool, I love it!
What do you say?
Wanna go?
Well...
Uh...
Hey...
See her?
Huh?
My sister Marie?
She's an angel.
Yeah?
Listen...
If you lay a finger on her, then you die!
Whoa!
Gosh Adlai.
Loves his sister a tad too much, but he's good people.
This here is Charmy Papitsen.
A big eater, but she's good people.
Mr. Vecha!
And this is Grey.
I don't really get him, but he's good people.
For sure.
Uh, hi.
Then there's Magnus Swing.
A street punk, but he's good people.
Scary!
And I am Finral Rulacase.
Lady killer.
And finally, we have the Black Bulls' fearless leader.
The Great Captain Yami Sugehiro!
What?
Know he's good people?
I'm really glad to be here, sir!
There are other members, of course.
But the rest are out on missions, or on leave, or I don't know.
Think you can play nice, newbie?
Yes, sir!
We're gonna get along so well!
Like I said before, it's really nice to meet you guys!
God, is he trying to kill me?
Right?
That's something I noticed before.
You're as loud as you are short, aren't you?
Yeah!
Shut up, kid.
Right, sorry!
Well, gang, let's go.
Give him a good workout, but try not to kill him.
Wait, what?
Did you hear him?
Uh-huh.
Yami wants us to make sure you get good workout.
That's just what I'm gonna do.
A pathetic runt like you, and from where, Hajj?
A village almost no one has ever heard of before.
Not much mana, either.
And you're the newest member of the Black Bulls?
You gotta be kidding me!
I don't know what some magic poor hick like you
could've possibly done to impress Yami.
Do you wanna wear the robe that'll prove you're a true member
of the Black Bulls?!
That's... a real Magic Knight squad robe.
It's... it's so, so cool.
Damn right it is.
So you want it?!
Yeah, I do!
Gimme!
Wow, you're really excited.
You want it that bad?
Okay.
But first, you need to earn the approval of Yami's chief subordinate.
Me, man among men, Magna Swing!
This marks your entry to the Black Bulls.
A true baptism by fire.
Say what?
Baptism?
All right, village boy.
Let's see how bad you want this robe.
You gotta earn it by completing every task I give you!
I'm ready!
Let's do this!
Oh, goody.
And another one of these ridiculous baptisms.
Oh, I want a baptism too!
My Marine.
Here we go, go, go!
First, I want to see your physical prowess!
Five thousand crunches!
You got it!
Five thousand push-ups!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Not yet!
I'm not done!
Oh!
How hard!
Gorilla, I'm not done!
No, I'm a Marine.
Here we go, go, go!
First, I want to see your physical prowess!
Five thousand crunches!
You got it!
Five thousand push-ups!
Oh, ow, ow!
Not yet!
I'm not done!
I'M NOT DONE!
Ah, precious angel.
Not that it's actually gonna do him any good.
But the kid's alright.
Yeah, his stamina and physical strength are seriously off the charts.
Too bad magic's all that matters.
How'd I do?
Not bad, Runt. Seems you're stronger than you look.
Okay, so I passed your test, right?
Then give me that room already!
Not so fast.
You think it's that simple?
We're not done yet, Village Boy.
There's one more test.
The last and most important of your baptism.
Here we go.
Using any skills at your disposal, whether they're magical or ordinary.
You must dodge or defend yourself against my attack magic.
If you can manage that, then you will pass.
You may consider yourself a true black bull.
And I will give you your robe.
Okay.
Right! I understand! I'll do my best!
Shut up!
Okay! Grab your grimoire and get ready!
Yes, sir!
Whoa! What's he got there?
So big!
Syria!
Cool!
You ready?
Ready!
Here we go!
Bring it on!
Let's see what you can do!
Take this!
Ah!
Ha!
You're pretty decent.
Yes, sir!
I'm gonna pass!
All right.
The real battle begins now!
So hot.
Here we go!
Play magic!
Exploding!
Fire!
Bell!
Are you serious?
Oh man, I'm dead.
Without conscious thought, Asta's brain realized something.
Thus far, he'd used his well-trained body, his kinetic vision, and his explosive power to slice through magic and destroy his foes.
But this time was different.
Magna's magic was too quick for Asta to intercept.
It's so fast.
Even if he did slice through it, the force of the attack would not die, and Asta would still absorb the full blow.
I can't block it!
When he knew he knew he was out of options, all thoughts shut down.
However, his body still refused to give up.
Asta had spent years training his body, and when faced with this final struggle...
Somehow, it found a way to survive.
Wow!
He did it!
Wow, did not see that coming.
That's the first time in a while that we haven't had to rescue the newbie.
He couldn't slice it with the blade's edge, so he hit it with the flat.
Asta had been shot!
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure how he died!
Wow, did not see that coming.
That's the first time in a while that we haven't had to rescue the newbie.
He couldn't slice it with the blade's edge, so he hit it with the flat.
Seems that sword can both cut through magic and reflect it.
Interesting.
I had no idea!
I knew I could slice through magic, but it turns out I can hit it too?!
This sword is awesome!
But jeez, that was close!
I almost died!
What the hell was he thinking, anyway?
Does he want to kill the new guy?
Wait, I didn't kill him, did I?!
What the hell did you just do, you crazy little runt?!
AHHHH!
He took a direct hit and he's still standing?!
I was able to dispel it in time, so I'm alright, but that doesn't change the fact that I was nearly offed by my own magic!
Wise you little...
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY SCARY!
You're really good! Wow!
Here, I thought you were just gonna block my magic and you fired it back at me!
You know, I think I kinda like you little Rasta!
It's some pasta!
Hey, sorry about calling you a magic poor hick earlier.
Hell, to be honest, I'm from the sticks myself.
Rayaka Village, just up from Hajj.
No way, really?
Rayaka is way out in the middle of nowhere!
Yeah, sure, says the kid from Hajj.
Oh, and just so you know, it's not that I have low magic power, I actually have none at all.
What was that?!
You've got no magic power?!
And you are still able to turn my magic against me?!
Uh, yeah. I guess so.
Well, that's even more amazing, then.
You're not just some runt. You're a real man.
What? That was really yummy!
That was amazing!
Okay! It's time for baptism part two!
Uh, what?
You have to take me on now!
You were very impressive out there. Nice kiddo.
Ah! Thank you!
I brought you something! Don't be shy, it's really yummy! Well?
Sure, okay.
Here, you can have half.
Well, maybe half of a half.
Cool, thanks!
Yummy!
Okay, okay.
Don't we still have some business to take care of?
Boring!
Here you go.
You weren't this fair and square, Asta.
What? You don't want it?
No! I do! I do! I do! I do!
This is really mine!
Well, what are you waiting for? Let's see how it looks.
And now...
It's the finishing touch.
Hey! Looks pretty good on you.
Right, Yami?
I don't think it's his color.
It's official now.
You're one of us.
You're a member of the Black Bulls.
Don't do anything that would bring shame to Yami.
Or to the Black Bulls.
Understood!
I'm so glad to be a part of this team!
Shut up, kid.
I'm sorry!
I'll be more careful from now on, sir!
What part of shut up do you not understand?
So I guess that's the other new recruit.
Little insect.
Kind of all some useful stuff!
HumorBU Church
Threeises Suez
Once again,
Some familiary
Concentregation
Auschwitz
Wastfeeding
Helen
Thank you.
Now get out.
Yes, Yami, sir.
I've finally been accepted as one of the Black Bulls.
What?
I'm not the only new recruit?
Black Clover, page seven.
Another new member.
My magic is never giving up!